<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Avalanche</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Avalanche</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 18:11:20 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Spiderman No Way Home Review</title>
      <link>/posts/spiderman-nwh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 18:11:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/spiderman-nwh/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a few months since the webslingers third movie has made its debut, lets review it! Cameos There were 4 cameos in the movie. The most wellknown being Andrew Garfields spiderman and Tobey Maguires Spiderman. (OOPS if you didn&amp;rsquo;t know about it also cry about it). Another one being Matt Murdock from the Netflix/MCU TV Show Daredevil. Matt didn&amp;rsquo;t play that big of a part, they really could have swapped him for any lawyer but it was a cool cameo for the people that watched and or enjoyed daredevil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Batman Movie Review</title>
      <link>/posts/the-batman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 17:51:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-batman/</guid>
      <description>The Batman is now on HBO max which means many people have now seen it. :)
The Batman was a movie that wasn&amp;rsquo;t like other DCEU movies. It was a lot more dark and dove into the past of Bruce Wayne. While we didn&amp;rsquo;t get to see much of him on screen, a lot of his actions through out the move were based on his past. The vibe of the movie was very enjoyable where most of the time in gotham it was either raining or very dark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Narrative Based on Novel &#39;Feed&#39;</title>
      <link>/posts/story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 17:46:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/story/</guid>
      <description>The Gone Land Long ago, before the revolution everything thrived, now I may be the last human left on earth. I have been living by myself for five years since my parents died in the year 4098. I was born here in the bunker and never have seen the outside world. My parents told me stories of the old days where everything was alive, now you die the moment you step out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anti Steal</title>
      <link>/plugins/anti-steal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 18:19:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/plugins/anti-steal/</guid>
      <description>Link to Plugin
Instructions Place a sign on a storage item to make it protected</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teleport</title>
      <link>/plugins/teleport/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 18:14:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/plugins/teleport/</guid>
      <description>Link to Plugin
Teleport /spawn - Teleports Player to spawn
/tpayes - Accepts Player Teleport Request
/tpano - Declines Player Teleport Request
/tpa off - Disables Teleport Requests
/tpa on - Enables Teleport Requests
Paid Commands
/tpa username - Sends a Request to Player to Teleport to Them
/tpahere username - Sends Request to Player to Teleport Them to You</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minecraft</title>
      <link>/posts/minecraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 18:33:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/minecraft/</guid>
      <description>Minecraft is a sandbox video game developed by Mojang Studios. The game was created by Markus &amp;ldquo;Notch&amp;rdquo; Persson in the Java programming language. Following several early private testing versions, it was first made public in May 2009 before fully releasing in November 2011, with Notch stepping down and Jens &amp;ldquo;Jeb&amp;rdquo; Bergensten taking over development. Minecraft has since been ported to several other platforms and is the best-selling video game of all time, with over 238 million copies sold and nearly 140 million monthly active users as of 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 16:05:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Discord: https://discord.gg/vqsWH7Hb9r
Twitch: https://www.twitch.tv/dablazelive</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadmap</title>
      <link>/posts/roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 17:07:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/roadmap/</guid>
      <description>As you may know the server had shutdown. This website will allow us to fund for a new server and keep running the server once it&amp;rsquo;s open.
#Website Launch
Aiming to launch this website by April 16 to fund the server
#Server Season 3
Aiming to launch the server by May 31</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Server Details</title>
      <link>/server/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 15:51:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/server/</guid>
      <description>Will be Added Soon</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 15:51:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about-us/</guid>
      <description>Made by Noehtnap Avalanche is a Minecraft server for people to play on version 1.18. It has a small community with interesting and fun people. The server is crossplay, meaning that both Java and Bedrock Editions can play! The Minecraft server has a dedicated Discord server too! In the Discord server you are able to talk to other players, without being connected to the Minecraft server! There are 3 owners, DaBlaze, Fenny and Dead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Season 2</title>
      <link>/posts/season-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 17:01:53 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/season-2/</guid>
      <description>Everyone thank you for an amazing first season. Even though we did run into a hacker we had a lot of FUN! The new season will start with a new host and Multi-Platform capability to allow more people to play!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Launch</title>
      <link>/posts/launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 16:51:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/launch/</guid>
      <description>The server if offically up! This marks the launch of Avalanche SMP!!!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
